feixudm.com 2018-08-13

# Privacy Policy | Lunarpages

Lunarpages takes your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy sets forth our commitment to you regarding your privacy and security on the Lunarpages website (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy will detail the categories of information we collect from Lunarpages users, how we use such information, and how you can access the information that we have and make changes or remove it. This Privacy Policy is issued based upon our commitment to you and in conformity with California Business and Professions Code section 22575. For EU residents, special considerations may apply as set forth below.

**Categories of Information Collected**

Lunarpages collects both personally identifiable information (which is information specific and personal to you) and non-personally identifiable information (which is aggregate information that does not identify you).

**Collection and Use of Information**

**General**

Lunarpages collects information from and about you as user of the Site. We collect this information (a) when you register as a customer; (b) when you request services offered by Lunarpages; (c) when you communicate with us about your account; and (d) when you access the Site. The information that we collect includes your name, address, telephone number, email address, billing information, URL information, IP Address, browser type, and other data relating to the sale, use and billing of our services. In addition to the uses described throughout this Privacy Policy, the information we collect relating to you will be used: (1) for the registration and management of your member account, including to provide the services that you have requested (2) for purposes of security, maintaining the Site and ensuring the best possible user experience, (3) to collect any outstanding balance on your account, (4) to enforce our rights and/or ensure your compliance with our Terms of Service, (5) to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our site, (6) to communicate with you on behalf of ourselves and our marketing partners, and (7) to share your personally identifiable information with our approved marketing partners for marketing purposes related to offers that we believe you may be interested in. We require all marketing partners to comply with the Federal CAN-SPAM Act, GDPR and all other applicable laws. We require that each such marketing partner provide a conspicuous opt-out link for your use to remove your information from their email list. Furthermore, if you wish us not to share your email address or other personally identifiable information you may contact us by email at [support@lunarpages.com](mailto:support@lunarpages.com).

**Surveys or Contests**

On occasion we provide hosting customers with the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

If the contest or survey requires, permits or is otherwise related to the submission by you to us of any story, artwork, photograph or other such material this information and material may be used to select a winner and tabulate survey results. In addition, we may use any such submission pursuant to the relevant portion of our Terms of Service to display to other hosting customers or non-hosting customers whether or not in conjunction with information from our advertisers or partners.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on the Lunarpages website. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. By your use of the Lunarpages website you consent to allow us to place cookies on your computer and to access them as you navigate our website.

We use session ID cookies which expire when you close your browser. These cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

**Links to Other Sites**

The Site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Lunarpages. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit and how it collects and uses your personally identifiable information.

**Lunarpages – Under 13 Privacy Statement  
Information Collection & Use**

Lunarpages does not specifically target the Site to children under 13 years of age. Nonetheless, all of the Site content is intended to be generally appropriate for children with the proper parental guidance and as such we encourage parents to explore this website together with their children and to discuss the information obtained.

**Your Websites**

Information that you post on the Internet or in public forums can be read, collected, or used by other users of the Internet, and could be used to identify you, contact you, send you unsolicited messages or for any other possible purpose. We have no control over the use of such information. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information you post and we caution you to consider all such information to be publicly available. If you believe that you have been contacted in a manner that is in violation of our Terms of Service please notify us and include all information you may have as to the nature of any communication that you received and the identity of the person initiating such communication. Please send all notices under this paragraph to [abuse@lunarpages.com](mailto:abuse@lunarpages.com).

According to our Terms of Service, misuse of such information by anyone, including you, can result in the termination of a user account.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. Information that you submit in relation to a financial transaction is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Information in our possession is maintained according to generally accepted industry standards. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Website, you may contact us at [support@lunarpages.com](mailto:support@lunarpages.com).

**Business Transitions**

In the event Lunarpages goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information via email at the address you have provided during registration.

**Third Party Data Collection**

Use of the Lunarpages website does not expose users to the collection of data by third parties directly. Lunarpages does not currently participate in any program to allow the sharing of data as to our user’s behavior within the Lunarpages systems.

**How to Access or Modify Your Information**

The Lunarpages Terms of Service requires that all customers keep their account information current at all times. However, the above collection practices may cause our systems to collect and maintain other information as described above pertaining to you in addition to your account information. As to any such additional information for Members or any information collected from individuals not yet a customer of Lunarpages, we provide the opportunity for you to determine, update and in some instances remove the data that we have collected. In order to determine whether we have any information connected to you, or to update your information, you may send an email to [support@lunarpages.com](mailto:support@lunarpages.com) with your user name and your email address. Please do not provide your password.

**Revisions to This Policy**

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here, place a notice on our homepage, and place a notice in other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you either here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page, at our option.

**European Union Residents – GDPR** :

The following additional provisions apply to Personally Identifiable Information  collected by Lunarapages  from European Union residents located therein at the time the data is collected (“PII” or “data”). For EU data subjects, in the event of any conflict between these provisions and those set forth above, these provisions shall control. The General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (“GDPR”) governs the processing and protection of your PII and affords you the following rights you can enforce by contacting Lunarpages through support@lunarpages.com:

  * You may access, update, or delete your PII via your Control Panel or by contacting us at [support@lunarpages.com](mailto:support@lunarpages.com). Thereafter, our retention of such information will depend upon the data necessary for any services purchased or otherwise required for our legitimate business purpose, legal or contractual record keeping requirements. You may request that we cease the use of your PII for marketing purposes also by contacting us at [support@lunarpages.com](mailto:support@lunarpages.com). Notwithstanding the forgoing, exceptions may apply for data maintained: 
    * Pursuant to any legal or contractual obligation;
    * In relation to resolving, defending or enforcing our rights;
    * For accurate business and financial reporting.
  * You may transfer your PII to another entity by contacting us at [support@lunarpages.com](mailto:support@lunarpages.com).
  * You may request that we cease processing your PII for marketing purposes by contacting us at [support@lunarpages.com](mailto:support@lunarpages.com).
  * Any questions concerning our GDPR policies may be directed to:

GDPR Compliance  
1908 N. Enterprise St.  
Anaheim, CA 92865  
legal@lunarpages.com

**Questions About the Lunarpages Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at:

Add2Net, Inc.  
Lunarpages Division  
1908 N. Enterprise St.  
Anaheim, CA 92865

Or via email at [support@lunarpages.com](mailto:support@lunarpages.com)

Version 6.0 – 20180524
